<resources>
    <string name="app_name">A2D2</string>
    <string name="home_screen">THIS A PRIVATE ORGANIZATION. IT IS NOT PART OF THE DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE OR ANY OF ITS COMPONENTS AND IT HAS NO GOVERNMENTAL STATUS.</string>
    <string name="request_ride_button">Request Ride</string>
    <string name="a2d2_rules_title">A2D2 Program Rules</string>
    <string name="a2d2_rules_text">1. A2D2 is a volunteer organization of airmen dedicated to reducing the number of DUIs in the Air Force. Use of this program should be your last resort, not your Plan A.\n\n2. If you find yourself with no safe alternative, simply press the “Request Driver” button. The app will use your current GPS location and you will receive a notification when a driver is dispatched.\n\n3. A2D2 drivers will only transport you to your home address. If you are making a request on behalf of a group, the driver is only required to take the group to a single address. If members of the group need to go to multiple homes, those individuals will need to make separate pickup requests.</string>
    <string name="a2d2_rules_button">Agree</string>
    <string name="dialog_allow">ALLOW</string>
    <string name="dialog_deny">DENY</string>
    <string name="dialog_okay">OKAY</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_LocationPermissionDenied">Location Permission Denied</string>
    <string name="location_dialog_text">Use Location?\n\nThis app wants to change</string>
    <string name="error_LocationPermissionDenied">You have not allowed the A2D2 app to access your GPS location. Without this permission, the app cannot function. Please go to your phone settings and enable the GPS permission.</string>
    <string name="error_DefaultError">An error has occurred</string>
    <string name="tv_group_size">Group Size</string>
    <string name="tv_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="button_request_driver">Request Driver</string>
    <string name="confirm_driver_request_title">Confirm Driver Request?</string>
    <string name="confirm_driver_request_body">Are you sure you want to dispatch a driver to your current location?</string>
    <string name="remarks_optional">Remarks (optional)</string>
    <string name="bacon_ipsum">Spicy jalapeno bacon ipsum dolor amet alcatra burgdoggen kevin sausage meatloaf, hamburger swine tongue filet mignon pastrami venison bresaola jerky. Meatball sirloin frankfurter, ham t-bone cow strip steak beef capicola ball tip. Picanha salami corned beef frankfurter, tri-tip fatback beef ribs. Short loin shank pork loin kevin, tail spare ribs ball tip picanha short ribs shoulder ground round brisket hamburger alcatra bacon. Meatball andouille fatback shoulder cow, tongue venison. Pork chop jowl biltong porchetta.</string>
    <string name="group_size">Group Size</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="activity_request_ride_name">Name</string>
    <string name="a2d2_field_required">Required*</string>
</resources>
